A Finding Aid to the Exhibition Records of the Contemporary Study Wing of the Finch College Museum of Art, 1943-1975, in the Archives of American Art
Archives of American Art
- Administrative Records, 1950-1975; Series 1; Archival Resource Key; 2.1 Linear feet Boxes 1-2, 22, OV 23
  - Oversized Administrative Records, Grants, New York State Council on the Arts Poster digitized with box 2, folder 3, 1969; Archival Resource Key (Box OV 23, Folder 1)
- Artist Files, 1958-1975; Series 2; Archival Resource Key; 2.4 Linear feet Boxes 3-4, 22, OV 23, FC 27-28
  Series is arranged in two sections, the general artist files, and the New York Arts Annual Calendar files. Varian's letters to galleries soliciting artist information are found in the 1964 correspondence of the Administrative Records in Series 1. Unsolicited letters with artist information enclosed can also be found in the correspondence files in that series. Additional records related to works in the permanent collection of the Finch College Museum are also found in series 1. Many of the exhibitions documented in series 4, Exhibition Files, also contain their own run of artist files specific to the exhibition, which tend to contain richer documentation than files in this series.
  Series includes a group of files created at the Contemporary Study Wing to be both a study collection for students of museum practice and a resource for exhibition planning, which are filed under the general artist files heading. The general artist files also contain documents related to contemporary artists whose works were in the Finch College Museum's permanent collection, and printed material on artists who were of interest to Elayne Varian. Many of the general artist files contain only one or two items, usually a résumé, exhibition announcement, and/or photograph of an artwork. A few of the files contain more substantial documentation, including multiple images of artworks, photographs of artists, correspondence, instructions regarding complex artworks, posters, publications by the artist, or artist's statements. Files for Jeff Dell contain 3 motion picture film reels (16 mm), two of which also have two videocassette access copies each (VHS and Digital Betacam). Where present, significant materials in the general artist files are noted in the folder listing.
  Also found is an incomplete run of questionnaires for the 1964 New York Arts Calendar Annual, which were completed by artists and often accompanied with printed material relating to exhibitions scheduled for that year. A letter explaining the donation of these records to the Contemporary Study Wing for their research value is filed with this set of records. Questionnaires are found for artists with surnames beginning with A through E, and M through S. The rest of the Arts Calendar questionnaires are not found in the collection. Occasionally artists represented in this part of the series also have a file in the general artist files.
  The bulk of this series has been digitized. Materials which have not been digitized include blank pages, blank versos of photographs, and duplicates, In some cases, exhibition catalogs and other publications have had their covers, title pages, and relevant paged digitized.
  The motion picture film "Happy Birthday Felisa" (1968), found in the file for artist Jeff Dell, has been digitized for reference use.
  - General, Archival Resource Key (Box 3)
    - Cecile Abish, 1969; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 1)
    - Vito Acconci, 1969-1971; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 2)
      Includes several photographs of performance works, including a typescript entitled "Private Piece for Elayne Varian" (1969).
    - Lee Adler, circa 1967-1969; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 3)
    - Josef Albers, 1964-1971; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 4)
    - Eleanor Antin, 1971-1973; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 5)
      Includes multiple postcards from Antin's "100 Boots" piece, as well as photographs and printed material related to other works.
    - Maggy Aldrich, 1964; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 6)
      Oversized item housed in box 22, folder 2.
    - Marit Guiness Aschan, 1974; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 7)
    - Mary Ascher, 1964-1967; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 8)
    - Elise Asher, 1973; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 9)
    - Edward Avedisian, 1971-1974; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 10)
    - Will Barnet, 1965; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 11)
    - Jack Beal, 1965; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 12)
    - Siri Berg, 1972-1974; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 13)
    - Henryk Berlewi, 1965; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 14)
      Oversized item in box 22, folder 2
    - Nell Blaine, 1968; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 15)
    - Seymour Boardman, 1967; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 16)
    - Mel Bochner, 1973; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 17)
    - Joe Brainard, 1965; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 18)
      Contains a copy of The Baby Book by Brainard and Kenward Elmslie
    - Warren Brandt, 1968, 1970; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 19)
    - Selma Brody, circa 1974; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 20)
    - Robert Bucker, 1964; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 21)
    - Sylvia Carewe, 1959-1968; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 22)
      Oversized material housed in OV 23, folder 2
    - Claudia Carrel, circa 1968; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 23)
    - Enrique Castro-Cid, circa 1964-1970; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 24)
      Oversized item housed in box 22, folder 2
    - Doris Chase, 1967-1970; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 25)
      Contains extensive correspondence between Chase and Elayne Varian. Oversized clippings housed in box 22, folder 2
    - Doris Chase, 1967-1970; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 26)
      Contains extensive correspondence between Chase and Elayne Varian.
    - Minna Citron, 1966; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 27)
    - Ross Coates, circa 1968; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 28)
    - Adele Cohen, 1973-1974; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 29)
    - George Cohen, 1964; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 30)
      Oversized poster moved to box 22, folder 2
    - Rosalind G. Cohen, circa 1962; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 31)
    - Joseph Cornell, 1967-1973; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 32)
      Contains correspondence with the Estate of Joseph Cornell following Cornell's death.
    - Hanne Darboven, 1974; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 33)
    - Jaime Davidovich, 1973; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 34)
      Oversized poster with handwritten note housed in OV 23, folder 3
    - Jeff Dell and Jeff Dell Film Service, Archival Resource Key (Box 3)
      - "Dodge City", ca. 1967; Archival Resource Key; 1 Film reel 16 mm (Item FC 27)
      - "Hush Hush Sweet City", circa 1967; Archival Resource Key; 1 Film reel Leader also labeled "Bob Monroe" 16 mm (Item FC 28)
      - "Happy Birthday Felisa", 1968; Archival Resource Key; 1 Videocassettes (VHS) Duplicate; 1 Videocassettes (Digital Betacam) Duplicate (Box 3, Folder 36)
        Videocassettes are duplicate access copies of original motion picture film.
      - "Happy Birthday Felisa", 1968; Archival Resource Key; 1 Film reel 16mm (Item FC 29)
    - Agnes Denes, circa 1969-1972; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 37)
      Contains letters, descriptions of artworks, photocopied typescript theoretical writings, clippings, and press releases.
    - Jim Dine, 1974; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 38)
    - Pat Diska, 1965-1966; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 39)
      Contains letters and a sketch by the artist
    - Seena Donneson, 1966, 1967, 1971; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 40)
      Oversized poster housed in OV 23, folder 4.
    - Jacob Drachler, circa 1966; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 41)
    - Josef Drapell, 1973-1974; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 42)
    - Jean Dubuffet, 1971; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 43)
    - Dale Eldred, circa 1967; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 44)
    - Ahron Elvaiah, circa 1964-circa 1970; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 45)
    - Jules Engel, circa 1968; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 46)
    - Frances Field, 1964; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 47)
    - Helen Frankenthaler, 1966; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 48)
    - Charles Frazier, circa 1965; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 49)
      Contains photocopied typescript, "Excerpts from a work journal on flying sculpture"
    - Sue Fuller, 1967; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 50)
    - Paul Gedeohn, circa 1966-1974; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 51)
    - Paul Georges, circa 1968; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 52)
    - Robert Goodnough, circa 1973; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 53)
    - Adolph Gottlieb, circa 1970; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 54)
    - Gertrude Greene, 1958; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 55)
    - Stephen Greene, 1963; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 56)
    - Dorothy Greene-Pepper, 1967-1968; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 57)
      Contains correspondence and typescript entitled "Instructions for the care of molded cloth sculptures."
    - Nancy Grossman, circa 1969; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 58)
    - Group of Six, circa 1972; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 59)
      Contains slides, photos, resumes, and published material from Stephen Greene, Phoebe Helman, Richard Stankiewicz, Richard Miller, Anthonyh Padovano, Charles Cajori, and Lennart Anderson, as well as a letter proposing an exhibition
    - Group of Six, circa 1972; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 60)
    - Group of Six, circa 1972; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 61)
    - Aaronel De Roy Gruber, 1965-1968; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 62)
      Contains correspondence, clippings, slides, photographs, printed material, and a reference statement written by Elayne Varian
    - Lee Hall, circa 1968; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 63)
    - Irene Hamar, 1965; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 64)
    - Hiroshi Hattori, circa 1969; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 65)
    - Eva Hesse, 1971; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 66)
      Oversized magazine article housed in box 22, folder 2
    - Dick Higgins, 1968 April; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 67)
      Contains "Something Else Newsletter," 1968 April
    - Charles Hinman, circa 1964; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 68)
    - Theo Hios, 1971; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 69)
    - Raymond Hitchcock, 1967, 1970; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 70)
      Contains correspondence and photographs of artwork; also a letter and photographs from Harry Weisburd
    - Frederic Hobbs, 1968; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 71)
    - Gerrit Hondius, 1970; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 72)
    - Budd Hopkins, circa 1969; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 73)
    - Nelson Howe, 1964-1971; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 74)
      Contains letters
    - Ralph Humphrey, 1971; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 75)
    - Richard Hunt, 1968; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 76)
    - Neil Jenney, 1968; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 77)
    - Ray Johnson, 1966-1968; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 78)
      Contains mail art, clippings, letters, and photocopied writings
    - Allen Jones, circa 1964; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 79)
    - George Bobby Jones, 1974; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 80)
    - Judith Kamen, 1965; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 81)
    - Jacques Kaplan, 1969-1972; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 82)
      Contains correspondence and clippings regarding "Fur Show"
    - Fredric Karoly, circa 1964; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 83)
    - Lila Katzen, 1969-1975; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 84)
      Contains clippings, press releases, photographs, and slides
    - Emily Kenas, circa 1965; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 85)
    - Elena Kepalas, 1972-1974; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 86)
    - Justin Knowles, circa 1966; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 87)
    - Sacha Kolin, 1971-1973; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 88)
      Contains correspondence regarding gifts and works on loan to the museum
    - Joseph Kosuth, circa 1967; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 89)
      Contains photographs of artworks
    - Kristen Kraa, circa 1964; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 90)
    - Yayoi Kusama, 1964-1968; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 91)
      Contains a letter from the artist
    - Gerald Laing, circa 1964; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 92)
    - Ellen Lanyon, circa 1962; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 93)
    - Charles Lassiter, 1965; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 94)
    - Leonid, 1973; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 95)
    - Josef Levi, circa 1966; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 96)
    - Les Levine, 1968-1969; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 97)
      Contains clippings, press releases, photographs, printed material, and poster. Oversized poster and magazine housed in OV 23, folder 5.
    - John Loring, circa 1967; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 98)
    - Sven Lukin, 1964; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 99)
    - Howard Mehring, 1968; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 100)
    - Carlos Merida, 1965; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 101)
    - D.M. Merrick, 1968; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 102)
    - Michael Metz, 1971; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 103)
    - Evelyn Metzger, 1965; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 104)
    - Ursula Meyer, 1967-1968; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 105)
    - Toto Meylon, 1974; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 106)
    - Jay Milder, 1964; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 107)
    - Guido Molinari, circa 1964; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 108)
    - Molla, circa 1965; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 109)
    - Symcho Moszkowicz, 1968; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 110)
      Contains photographs of the artist
    - Bruce Nauman, circa 1970; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 111)
    - Don Nice, circa 1964; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 112)
    - Isamu Noguchi, circa 1967; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 113)
    - Earl Olsen, 1965; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 114)
    - George Ortman, circa 1971; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 115)
    - Alfonso Ossorio, 1969; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 116)
    - Anthony Padovano, 1960-1972; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 117)
    - Barbara Phillips Perle, circa 1974; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 118)
    - William Pettet, 1974; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 119)
    - Bernard Pfriem, 1967, 1974; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 120)
      Oversized poster housed in OV 23, folder 6.
  - General, Archival Resource Key (Box 4)
    - Lil Picard, 1971; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 1)
      Contains letters and photocopied writings
    - Pablo Picasso, 1965; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 2)
    - Roberto Pignataro, 1969; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 3)
      Contains slides.
    - Paul Pollaro, 1967-1972; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 4)
    - Thomas Prentiss, circa 1967; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 5)
    - Raquel Rabinovich, circa 1966; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 6)
    - Edward Randel, circa 1968; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 7)
      Contains instructions and technical information about light/motion work "Hegira"
    - Antonio Recalcati, circa 1966; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 8)
    - Odilon Redon, 1967; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 9)
    - Philip Reisman, 1967; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 10)
    - Jeanne Reynal, circa 1964; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 11)
    - James Ridlon, 1973-1974; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 12)
    - Bridget Riley, 1964; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 13)
    - Esther Rolick, 1968; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 14)
    - Seymour Rosenthal, 1966; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 15)
      Oversized poster in OV 23, folder 7.
    - Stephen Rosenthal, 1970-1975; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 16)
      Contains correspondence, photographs, and a typescript artist's statement
    - James Russell, 1965; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 17)
    - Graham Redgrave Rust, 1965; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 18)
    - Freida Savitz, circa 1965-circa 1970; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 19)
    - Joseph Schillinger, 1966-1971; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 20)
      Contains correspondence with Schillinger's widow, Frances Schillinger
    - Miriam Schapiro, 1971; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 21)
    - Roslyn Schomer, 1972; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 22)
    - Theresa Schwartz, 1966; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 23)
      Contains a letter, photographs, and a magazine article
    - James Seawright, 1966-1967; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 24)
    - Roger Selchow, 1974; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 25)
      Contains correspondence
    - Thomas Sills, 1974; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 26)
    - Arlie Sinaiko, 1969; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 27)
    - Esther Forman Singer, 1970; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 28)
    - Richard Smith, circa 1971; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 29)
    - Tony Smith, 1971; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 30)
      Contains photographs of installation
    - Robert Smithson, 1974; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 31)
    - Alan Sondheim, 1971; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 32)
    - Jack Sonenberg, 1972-1973; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 33)
    - Harry Soviak, 1964-1971; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 34)
    - Norma Jeas Squires, 1965; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 35)
      Contains photographs
    - Sala Staw, circa 1968-1970; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 36)
    - Harold Stevenson, 1964; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 37)
    - Risa (Rissa Sussman), 1971; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 38)
      Contains correspondence, contact sheets and instructions for dismantling sculpture
    - Joan Tausik, 1966; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 39)
    - Helen Thomas, 1973; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 40)
    - George Tooker, circa 1964; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 41)
    - Anthony Tortora, 1968; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 42)
    - Cy Twombly, circa 1970; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 43)
    - Stella Waitzkin, circa 1974; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 44)
    - Judy Waterman, 1974; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 45)
    - Jeanne Whorrall, 1965; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 46)
    - John Wilde, circa 1963; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 47)
    - John Willenbecher, 1964-1974; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 48)
      Contains letter from the artist. Oversized poster housed in box 22, folder 2.
    - Neil Williams, circa 1964; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 49)
  - New York Arts Calendar Annual, Archival Resource Key (Box 4)
    - Letter Describing Donation of Artist Files, 1964; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 50)
    - Antonakos - Elliott, 1963-1964; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 51)
      Also contains a form for the artist Leonid
    - McAfee - McNeill, 1963-1964; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 52)
    - Meigs - Mieczkowski, 1963-1964; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 53)
    - Miller - Mitchell, 1963-1964; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 54)
    - Model - Morang, 1963-1964; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 55)
    - Morera - Mueller, 1963-1964; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 56)
    - Muhl - Nagare, 1963-1964; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 57)
    - Nachumi - Nelson, 1963-1964; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 58)
    - Neujean - Noyer, 1963-1964; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 59)
    - Okada - Oxtoby, 1963-1964; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 60)
    - Parker - Pattison, 1963-1964; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 61)
    - Pereira - Phillips, 1963-1964; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 62)
    - Pickhardt - Pitigliani, 1963-1964; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 63)
    - Pollack - Quirt, 1963-1964; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 64)
    - Radulovic - Reder, 1963-1964; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 65)
    - Reed - Rodin, 1963-1964; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 66)
    - Rodriguez - Rosso, 1963-1964; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 67)
    - Rothbort - Ryman, 1963-1964; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 68)
    - Saleme - Sawyer, 1963-1964; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 69)
    - Schaeffer - Schneider, 1963-1964; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 70)
    - Schoener - Seley, 1963-1964; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 71)
    - Seliger - Schurr, 1963-1964; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 72)
    - Schwartz - Sheppard, 1963-1964; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 73)
    - Sherbeck - Snow, 1963-1964; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 74)
    - Solotaire - Spiro, 1963-1964; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 75)
    - Spoerri - Stefanelli, 1963-1964; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 76)
    - Stern - Streeter, 1963-1964; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 77)
    - Subirachs - Swinson, 1963-1964; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 78)
  - Oversized Maggy Aldrich Poster digitized with box 3, folder 6, 1964; Archival Resource Key (Box 22, Folder 2)
  - Oversized Henryk Berlewi Catalog digitized with box 3, folder 14, 1965; Archival Resource Key (Box 22, Folder 2)
  - Oversized Enrique Castro-Cid Poster digitized with box 3, folder 24, 1963; Archival Resource Key (Box 22, Folder 2)
  - Oversized Doris Chase Clippings digitized with box 3, folder 25, 1969-1970; Archival Resource Key (Box 22, Folder 2)
  - Oversized George Cohen Poster digitized with box 3, folder 30, 1964; Archival Resource Key (Box 22, Folder 2)
  - Oversized Eva Hesse Article digitized with box 3, folder 66, 1971; Archival Resource Key (Box 22, Folder 2)
  - Oversized John Willenbacher Poster digitized with box 4, folder 48, circa 1964; Archival Resource Key (Box 22, Folder 2)
  - Oversized Sylvia Carewe Material digitized with box 3, folder 22, 1959-1968; Archival Resource Key (Box OV 23, Folder 2)
  - Oversized Jaime Davidovich Poster digitized with box 3, folder 34, 1973; Archival Resource Key (Box OV 23, Folder 3)
  - Oversized Seena Donneson Poster digitized with box 3, folder 40, 1966; Archival Resource Key (Box OV 23, Folder 4)
  - Oversized Les Levine Material digitized with box 3, folder 97, 1968-1969; Archival Resource Key (Box OV 23, Folder 5)
  - Oversized Bernard Pfriem Poster digitized with box 3, folder 120, 1967; Archival Resource Key (Box OV 23, Folder 6)
  - Oversized Seymour Rosenthal Poster digitized with box 4, folder 15, 1966; Archival Resource Key (Box OV 23, Folder 7)
- Elayne Varian Personal Papers, 1965-1970; Series 3; Archival Resource Key; 1.3 Linear feet Boxes 5-6
  The bulk of the material in this series has been digitized, except for duplicates.
  All of the sound recordings in this series have been digitized for research use.
  Series consists of records related to curatorial, teaching, and writing projects of Elayne Varian that were not undertaken in her role at Finch College.
  Curatorial projects include the exhibition Art Today (1967), a juried show at the New York State Fair; a series of art film screenings held at the Everson Museum of Art of Syracuse University, and an exhibition at Guild Hall in East Hampton featuring local artists over the age of 60.